A Guide to the Alexandria School of Nursing Collection 1894-1987
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING FACULTY AND STAFF N.D., PHOTOGRAPHS (11) (Box-folder 004-018)
- COMMENCEMENT INVITATIONS 1956-1975, PRINTED CARDS (2) (Box-folder 004-019)
- ARTICLES RE: ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLOSING 1987, NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS (P) (4) (Box-folder 004-020)
- SENIOR BREAKFAST PROGRAM 1987/06/05, PROGRAM (Box-folder 004-021)
- COMMENCEMENT PROGRAM 1987/06/05, PROGRAM (Box-folder 004-022)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CAPPING/PINNING CEREMONY PRINT N.D., PRINT (Box-folder 004-023)
- POSTURE FUNDAMENTALS 1946/ca., PAMPHLET PAGES (Box-folder 004-024)
- "THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN NURSING AND THE HOSPITAL ORGANIZATIONAL ENVIRONMENT, NURSING STUDY; LETTER FROM ELEANOR G. FELDBAUM TO EDITH HARPER" 1975, TMs (2), TLS" (Box-folder 004-025)
- MATERIALS RE: ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING FEES 1967-1973, TMs (Box-folder 004-026)
- MATERIALS RE: ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLOSING 1984, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING, TL" (Box-folder 004-027)
  THE ALEXANDRIA JOURNAL
- STUDENT NURSE TO GET FIRST POWELL AWARD 1952, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 004-028)
- "NURSES HOUSE, INC." 1974/12/ca., PAMPHLET (Box-folder 004-029)
- A FIRST SHINGLE OF ITS KIND? 1971/10/13, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 004-030)
  THE EVENING STAR
- MALE NURSE OVERTURNS ANOTHER SEX BARRIER 1972/04/07, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (Box-folder 004-031)
  THE WASHINGTON POST
- CENTERSCOPE (SUMMER 1982) 1982, NEWSLETTER (Box-folder 004-032)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING POLICY MANUAL/STUDENT HANDBOOK 1964/07, TMs (Box-folder 004-033)
- UNIDENTIFIED GROUNDBREAKING N.D., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 005-001)
- ADVISERS HANDBOOK - NATIONAL STUDENT NURSES' ASSOCIATION 1966, TMs (Box-folder 005-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SERVICE AWARDS DINNER PROGRAMS 1967-1984, PROGRAMS (15) (Box-folder 005-003)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL CHARTER AND BY-LAWS 1955-1975, PAMPHLETS (2) (Box-folder 005-004)
- "ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING FACULTY HANDBOOK, POLICY MANUAL" 1981-1985, TMs (2) (Box-folder 005-005)
- MISCELLANEOUS MEMOS 1962-1987, TMemo (5) (Box-folder 005-006)
- MISCELLANEOUS PROGRAMS 1972-1977, PROGRAMS (4) (Box-folder 005-007)
- MISCELLANEOUS MATERIALS RE: CEREMONIES N.D., TMs (2), AMs, PRINTED SONG" (Box-folder 005-008)
- "MISCELLANEOUS NEWSPAPER CLIPPINGS, NEWSLETTERS, PHOTOGRAPHS, CORRESPONDENCE" 1974-1986, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING, NEWSLETTER (P), PHOTOGRAPH, TLS" (Box-folder 005-009)
- "STUDENT NURSES ASSOCIATION OF VIRGINIA ANNUAL CONVENTION PROGRAM, SNAV NEWSLETTER" 1976-1981, PROGRAM, NEWSLETTER" (Box-folder 005-010)
- CAPPING 1967-1972, PHOTOGRAPHS (5) (Box-folder 005-011)
- CAPPING CEREMONIES N.D., PHOTOGRAPHS (9) (Box-folder 005-012)
- RECRUITMENT N.D., TMs (Box-folder 005-013)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING COMMENCEMENT AND CLASS PHOTOGRAPHS N.D., PHOTOGRAPHS (42) (Box-folder 005-014)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL HIGHLIGHTS 1987/06/29, NEWSLETTER (Box-folder 005-015)
- HISTORY OF THE ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING 1980/ca., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 005-016)
- CAPPING AN ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL TRADITION 1985/04/15, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING (P) (Box-folder 005-017)
- REGULATIONS OF THE ALEXANDRIA INFIRMARY N.D., PAMPHLET PAGES (P) (3) (Box-folder 005-018)
- "ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL 110TH YEAR - A PROUD HISTORY, A BRIGHT FUTURE" 1983/04/15, NEWSPAPER (Box-folder 005-019)
- "BLESS THESE CAPS, LET THERE BE PEACE ON EARTH (SONGS)" N.D., AMs (Box-folder 005-020)
- HISTORY OF THE STUDENT UNIFORM 1987, PAMPHLET PAGE (P) (Box-folder 005-021)
- FACTS ABOUT THE NEW ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL N.D., PAMPHLET (Box-folder 005-022)
- "CHARTER AND BY-LAWS, ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL" 1955/08/12, PAMPHLET (Box-folder 005-023)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL HIGHLIGHTS 1987/04/27, NEWSLETTER (Box-folder 005-024)
- "NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF NURSING MISSION, STRUCTURE, AND GENERAL PROGRAMS" N.D., TMs (Box-folder 005-025)
- GUIDELINES FOR FACULTY ADVISORS TO CLASSES N.D., TMs (Box-folder 005-026)
- CANDLE LIGHTING SERVICE N.D., TMs (Box-folder 005-027)
- CAPPING CEREMONY PROGRAMS 1981-1984, PROGRAMS (4) (Box-folder 005-028)
- LEVEL OBJECTIVES 1981/ca., TMs (Box-folder 005-029)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING STUDENT AND GRADUATE LIST 1986/ca., TMs (Box-folder 005-030)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS PHOTOGRAPHS PAGE PROOFS 1987/ca., PHOTOGRAPHS (P) (Box-folder 005-031)
- CHARACTERISTICS OF DIPLOMA EDUCATION IN NURSING N.D., TMs (Box-folder 005-032)
- MATERIALS RE: COST SURVEY OF SCHOOLS OF NURSING 1973, TMs (Box-folder 005-033)
- MISCELLANEOUS PHOTOGRAPHS N.D., PHOTOGRAPHS (32) (Box-folder 005-034)
- "COMMENCEMENT PROGRAM, MISCELLANEOUS MATERIALS" 1987, PROGRAM, PAGE PROOFS (P) (4)" (Box-folder 005-035)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL HIGHLIGHTS 1987/04/27-06/29, NEWSLETTERS (2) (Box-folder 005-036)
- "THE ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING: A HISTORY FROM 1894 UNTIL 1915, THE ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING 1894-1987" 1987/ca., TMs (2) (Box-folder 005-037)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING ALUMNI DIRECTORY 1896-1987 1987, TMs (Box-folder 005-038)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CURRICULUM ROTATION PLANS FILES--OUTDATED 1956-1966/ca., TMs, AMs" (Box-folder 006-001)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CURRICULUM EVALUATION FILES 1984/ca., TMs (Box-folder 006-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING HISTORICAL COLLECTIONS/ARCHIVAL FILES 1987/ca., TMs, AMs" (Box-folder 006-003)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING HISTORY AND CLASS LISTS 1987/ca., TMs (5) (Box-folder 006-004)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING MISCELLANEOUS FILES 1987/ca., TMs, AMs" (Box-folder 006-005)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING MISCELLANEOUS PHOTOGRAPHS 1987/ca., PHOTOGRAPHS (29) (Box-folder 006-006)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING RECRUITMENT FILE 1960-1986/ca., TMs (Box-folder 006-007)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING ALUMNI DIRECTORY 1896-1987 1987, TMs (Box-folder 006-008)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSLETTERS AND PAMPHLET 1968-1987, NEWSLETTERS (5), PAMPHLET" (Box-folder 006-009)
- "A.G. UHLER TO BROTHER,;ALEXANDRIA-WASHINGTON LODGE, NO. 22, A.F. AND A.M." 1916/09/11, APC (Box-folder 006-010)
- TRIBUTE TO GORMAN CARLIN RIDGELY 1976/04/31, PROGRAM (Box-folder 006-011)
- TRAINING SCHOOL RECORD 1909-1921, LEDGER (Box-folder 007-001)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL ALUMNAE MINUTES 1918-1946, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 007-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL ALUMNAE MINUTES 1932-1946, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 007-003)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING ALUMNI DIRECTORY 1896-1987 1987, TMs (Box-folder 007-004)
- DIPLOMA NURSING STUDENTS' REPORTS OF THEIR FEELINGS IN THE CLINICAL LEARNING SITUATION BY MARGARET J. MCCABE 1973/05, TMs (Box-folder 007-005)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL HIGHLIGHTS 1987-1988, NEWSLETTERS (3) (Box-folder 007-006)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CAPPING/PINNING CEREMONY PRINTS N.D., PRINTS (3) (Box-folder 007-007)
- MISCELLANEOUS FILES 1987, NEWSPAPER CLIPPING, AN, INVOICE" (Box-folder 007-008)
- "REUNION BRUNCH PROGRAM, CLOSING ACTIVITIES INVITATION" 1987/O6/05-06, PROGRAM, PRINTED CARD" (Box-folder 007-009)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING COMMENCEMENT N.D., PHOTOGRAPHS (6) (Box-folder 007-010)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1900 1900/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-001)
- MARTHA THORNTON ASHTON - ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1902 1970/08/24, PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1908 1908/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-003)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1912 1912/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-004)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1913 1913/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-005)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1915 1915/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-006)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1916 1916/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-007)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF JUNE 1917 1917/06/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-008)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1924 1924/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-009)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1928 1928/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-010)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1931 1931/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-011)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1946 1946/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-012)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1947 1947/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-013)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF MARCH 1948 1948/04/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-014)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF SEPTEMBER 1948 1948/09/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-015)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1950 1950/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-016)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1951 1951/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-017)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1952 1952/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-018)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1953 1953/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-019)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1954 1954/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-020)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1955 1955/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-021)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1956 1956/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-022)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1957 1957/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-023)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1958 1958/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-024)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1959 1959/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-025)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1960 1960/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-026)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1961 1961/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-027)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1962 1962/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-028)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1963 1963/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-029)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1964 1964/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-030)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1965 1965/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-031)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1966 1966/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-032)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1967 1967/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-033)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1968 1968/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-034)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1969 1969/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-035)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1970 1970/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-036)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1971 1971/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-037)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1972 1972/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-038)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1973 1973/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-039)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1974 1974/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-040)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1975 1975/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-041)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1976 1976/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-042)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1977 1977/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-043)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1978 1978/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-044)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1979 1979/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-045)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1980 1980/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-046)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1981 1981/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-047)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1982 1982/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-048)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1983 1983/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-049)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1984 1984/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-050)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1985 1985/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-051)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1986 1986/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-052)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1987 1987/ca., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-053)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CARTER HALL N.D., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-054)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING BUILDING N.D., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 008-055)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING PHOTOGRAPHS (MOUNTED ON PAGE PROOFS) 1987/ca., PHOTOGRAPHS (15) (Box-folder 008-056)
- MISCELLANEOUS SLIDES OF ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING 1973-1976/ca., SLIDES (91) IN 3 BOXES (Box-folder 009-001)
- MISCELLANEOUS SLIDES OF ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING 1973/01/ca., SLIDES (189) IN 4 BOXES (Box-folder 009-002)
- MISCELLANEOUS SLIDES OF ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING 1973-1976/ca., SLIDES (126) IN 4 BOXES (Box-folder 009-003)
- THE REAL HERITAGE N.D., FILMSTRIP (Box-folder 010-001)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING PRESENTS 'THE REAL HERITAGE' N.D., AUDIO TAPE (Box-folder 010-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING PRESENTS 'THE REAL HERITAGE' N.D., AUDIO TAPE, FILMSTRIP" (Box-folder 010-003)
- "ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CAPPING PROGRAM CLASS OF 1961 RECORDED AT DOWNTOWN BAPTIST CHURCH, ALEXANDRIA, VIRGINIA" 1959/04/15, AUDIO TAPE (Box-folder 010-004)
- POTTER'S COMPEND OF HUMAN ANATOMY REVISED BY D. GREGG METHENY 1915, MONOGRAPH (Box-folder 010-005)
  EIGHTH EDITION, PHILADELPHIA, P. BLAKISTON'S SONS AND CO., 1012 WALNUT STREET; BLAKISTON'S ?QUIZ-COMPENDS?; LEE M. HUTCHINS - ARMY MEDICAL SCHOOL
- "NURSING OF CHILDREN BY GLADYS SELLEW IN COLLABORATION WITH SISTER ANNETTE WALTERS, AND SISTER ANN HARVEY" 1949, MONOGRAPH (Box-folder 010-006)
  SIXTH EDITION, ILLUSTRATED, PHILADELPHIA AND LONDON, W.B. SAUNDERS COMPANY
- "AN INTRODUCTION TO MATERIA MEDICA AND PHARMACOLOGY, 5TH EDITION BY ELSIE E. KRUG AND HUGH ALISTER MCGUIGAN" 1948, MONOGRAPH (Box-folder 010-007)
  5TH EDITION, ST. LOUIS, THE C.V. MOSBY COMPANY; ROSEMARY MORGAN
- THE ART AND SCIENCE OF NURSING BY ELLA L. ROTHWEILER AND JEAN MARTIN WHITE 1947, MONOGRAPH (Box-folder 010-008)
  THIRD REVISED EDITION, PHILADELPHIA, F.A. DAVIS COMPANY, PUBLISHERS; ROSEMARY MORGAN
- "SURGICAL NURSING BY ROBERT K. FELTER, FRANCES WEST, AND LYDIA M. ZETZSCHE" 1948, MONOGRAPH (Box-folder 010-009)
  FIFTH EDITION, PHILADELPHIA, F.A. DAVIS COMPANY, PUBLISHERS; ROSEMARY MORGAN
- "SURGICAL NURSING BY ROBERT K. FELTER, FRANCES WEST, AND LYDIA M. ZETZSCHE" 1949, MONOGRAPH (Box-folder 010-010)
  FIFTH EDITION, PHILADELPHIA, F.A. DAVIS COMPANY, PUBLISHERS; ANNE BALLARD
- "CARDIAC AND VASCULAR DISEASES VOLUME I EDITED BY HADLEY L. CONN, JR. AND ORVILLE HORWITZ" 1971, MONOGRAPH (Box-folder 010-011)
  PHILADELPHIA, LEA AND FEBIGER; SALLY NESS
- FLORENCE NIGHTINGALE BY ELSPETH HUXLEY 1975, MONOGRAPH (Box-folder 010-012)
  NEW YORK, G.P. PUTNAM'S SONS; ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL HEALTH SCIENCES LIBRARY
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL - OVER 120 YEARS OF MEDICAL PROGRESS - 1872 1992, VIDEOTAPE (Box-folder 010-013)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING PINS N.D., ARTIFACTS (27) (Box-folder 011-001)
  7 HONOR PINS, 8 ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL LAMP PINS, 7 ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING DOUBLE PINS WITH CHAIN, 1 WE CARE PIN, 1 A+ PIN, 1 BILL OF RIGHTS, 2 PINS BELONGING TO ELSIE TULLOCH
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING PINNING CEREMONY ROSE N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 011-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING LAMP N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 011-003)
  CERAMIC
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING LAMP N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 011-004)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING LAMP N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 011-005)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING LAMP N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 011-006)
  METAL
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--'THE WHITE LOG' [replaced with copy in better shape which is in Box 19.] 1954, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 011-007)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK [replaced with copy in better shape which is in Box 19.] 1977, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 011-008)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK [placed in Box 19 with the rest of the yearbooks.] 1987, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 011-009)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CAPS N.D., ARTIFACTS (8) (Box-folder 012-001)
  3 FOLDED CAPS, 3 UNFOLDED CAPS, 2 GAUZE CAPS
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING UNIFORM, 120TH ANNIVERSARY PHOTO, "NURSING DUTIES IN 1897" N.D., ARTIFACTS (4), PHOTO (1), DOCUMENT (1) (Box-folder 013-001)
  1 GREY COTTON DRESS WITH LACE AND VELVET TRIM, 1 BLACK VELVET SASH, 1 LACE COLLAR WITH VELVET TRIM, 1 GATHERED PIECE OF LACE (ON LOAN TO ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL DECEMBER 1992). PHOTO OF THE 120TH ANNIVERSARY OF THE ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL IS IN BOX. DOCUMENT IS ENTITLED "NURSING DUTIES IN 1897" AND ON FOAM BOARD.
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING UNIFORM [LABELS READ 'HELEN L. CALL'] N.D., ARTIFACTS (18) (Box-folder 014-001)
  1 BLUE AND WHITE STRIPED DRESS, 2 COLLAR ATTACHMENTS WITH BUTTONHOLES, 1 UNFOLDED CAP, 1 COLLAR, 1 APRON/SMOCK WITH AA, 5 BUTTONS, 7 SAFETY PINS (ON LOAN DECEMBER 1992 TO ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL EXCEPT FOR APRON/SMOCK) BLUE AND WHITE STRIPED DRESS WITH MISS SHERMAN TAG, 1 APRON/SMOCK WITH MISS SHERMAN TAG.
- MISCELLANEOUS UNIFORM ACCESSORIES N.D., ARTIFACTS (15) (Box-folder 015-001)
  1 DARK BLUE VELVET RIBBON, 1 PIECE OF BLUE VELVET FABRIC, 1 PIECE OF PATTERNED BLUE FABRIC, 12 ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING PATCHES
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING UNIFORM N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 015-002)
  1 LIGHT BLUE AND WHITE DRESS WITH APRON/SMOCK [LABEL READS '10']
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING UNIFORM N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 015-003)
  1 LIGHT BLUE AND WHITE DRESS [LABEL READS 'CLARISSA']
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING UNIFORM N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 015-004)
  1 BLUE AND WHITE DRESS [LABEL READS 'PROFILES INC. PHILADELPHIA, PA.']
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING UNIFORM ACCESSORIES N.D., ARTIFACTS (4) (Box-folder 016-001)
  1 WHITE APRON/SMOCK ['CARTER HALL' AND UNINTELLIGIBLE WORDS WRITTEN INSIDE WAIST], 1 WHITE SKIRT, 1 APRON FRONT, 1 HAT PIN
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING UNIFORM N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 016-002)
  1 BLUE AND WHITE STRIPED DRESS, LONG SLEEVE
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING UNIFORM N.D., ARTIFACT (Box-folder 016-003)
  1 BLUE AND WHITE STRIPED DRESS, SHORT SLEEVE [MISSING FRONT BUTTONS]
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL 100TH ANNIVERSARY 1871-1971 'WE'VE COME A LONG WAY' 1971, DRAWING IN FRAME (Box-folder 017-001)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK ENDSHEETS 1987/ca., PHOTOGRAPHS (2) ON 1 SHEET (Box-folder 017-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK ENDSHEETS 1987/ca., PHOTOGRAPHS (2) (Box-folder 017-003)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS N.D., PHOTOGRAPH (Box-folder 017-004)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CLASS OF 1973 1973/ca., PHOTOGRAPH IN FRAME (Box-folder 017-005)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING STUDENT GOVERNMENT PRESIDENTS 1982-1986, PLAQUE (Box-folder 017-006)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING STUDENT GOVERNMENT PRESIDENTS 1970-1982, PLAQUE (Box-folder 017-007)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING STUDENT GOVERNMENT PRESIDENTS 1952-1970, PLAQUE (Box-folder 017-008)
- BONNET N.D., CLOTH BONNET WITH BLACK VELVET BAND (Box-folder 018-001)
  THE BONNET IS PART OF THE NURSING UNIFORM IN BOX 14 WITH MISS SHERMAN TAG.
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--THE "WHITE LOG" 1948, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 019-001)
  THE FIRST ISSUE OF THE "WHITE LOG"
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--THE "WHITE LOG" 1951, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 019-002)
  THE SECOND ISSUE OF THE "WHITE LOG"
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"THE WHITE LOG" 1952, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 019-003)
  THIRD EDITION ORIGINALLY DONATED BY FRANCES SINDLINGER RICKER, CLASS OF 1952 ON 6/24/86. INCLUDES 1952 COMMENCEMENT PROGRAM.
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--THE "WHITE LOG" 1954, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 019-004)
  FIFTH EDITION
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1968-69, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 019-005)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1970, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 019-006)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1973, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 019-007)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1975, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 019-008)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1976, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 020-001)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK 1977, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 020-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1978, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 020-003)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1978-79, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 020-004)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1979-80, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 020-005)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1980-81, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 020-006)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK 1981-82, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 020-007)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK 1983, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 021-001)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1983-84, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 021-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK 1984-85, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 021-003)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--"SUNDOWN" 1985-86, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 021-004)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING YEARBOOK--1894-1987 CELEBRATING A PROUD HISTORY 1987, YEARBOOK (Box-folder 021-005)
  INCLUDES EARLY PHOTOS AND HISTORY
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING n.d., PATCH (Box-folder 021-006)
  PATCH IS NAVY WITH WHITE EMBROIDERY, 3" IN DIAMETER
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING ADMISSIONS AND RECRUITMENT COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS 1970-76 AND RECRUITMENT COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS 1976-84 1970-84, TMs (Box-folder 022-001)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING ADMISSIONS COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS 1976-86, TMs (Box-folder 022-002)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING ADMISSIONS COMMITTEE MINUTES 1984-87, TMs (Box-folder 022-003)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING ADVISORY COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS 1976-80, TMs (Box-folder 022-004)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING COOPERATING AGENCIES 1984-87, TMs (Box-folder 022-005)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CURRICULUM COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS 1964-87, TMs (Box-folder 022-006)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING CURRICULUM COMMITTEE MINUTES 1984-87, TMs (Box-folder 022-007)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING ENROLLMENT NOTEBOOK 1985-87, NOTEBOOK (Box-folder 022-008)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING FACULTY DEVELOPMENT (INSERVICE) COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS 1968-86 AND MINUTES 1984-86 1968-86, TMs (Box-folder 022-009)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING FACULTY ORGANIZATION 1984-87, TMs (Box-folder 022-010)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING LIBRARY 1966-86, TMs (Box-folder 022-011)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING STUDENT GOVERNMENT ORGANIZATION ANNUAL REPORTS, COUNCIL MEETING MINUTES, ASSEMBLY MEETING MINUTES, SNAV (STUDENT NURSES ASSOCIATION OF VIRGINIA) ANNUAL REPORTS, CLASS REPORTS 1980-87, TMs (Box-folder 022-012)
- ALEXANDRIA HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING STUDENT SERVICES COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS 1976-87 AND MINUTES 1984-87 1976-87, TMs (Box-folder 022-013)